rcmoment.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

Last Modified:  [June 20, 2018] 

This Privacy Statement explains how RCMOMENTcollect,use,share and process your information. 

**1.Collection and Use of Personal Data**

Personal data is information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you.Personal data also includes anonymous data that is linked to information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you.Personal data does not include data that has been irreversibly anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer enable us,whether in combination with other information or otherwise,to identify you. 

Here is a description of the types of personal data we may collect and how we may use it: 

_1.1What Personal Data We Collect  _ ****

Depending on the products and services you use,we collect different kinds of personal data from or about you.

Data you provide: We collect the personal data you provide when you use our products and services or otherwise interact with us,such as when you create an account,contact us 

,participate in an online survey,use our online help or online chat tool. 

Data about payments: If you make a purchase,we collect personal data in connection with the purchase.This data including your payment data,such as your credit or debit card number and other card information,and other account and authentication information,as well as billing,shipping,and contact details. 

Data about use of our services and products: When you visit our websites,we may collect data about the type of device you use,your device's unique identifier, the IP address of your device, your operating system, the type of Internet browser that you use, usage information, diagnostic information, and location information from or about the computers, phones, or other devices on which you install or access our products or services. Where available, our services may use GPS, your IP address, and other technologies to determine a device's approximate location to allow us to improve our products and services. 

_1.2How We Use Your Personal Data  _

Generally speaking,we use personal data to provide,improve,and develop our products and services,to communicate with you,to offer you targeted advertisements and services,and to protect us and our customers. 

RCMENT processes and determines how to process your personal data as data controller for the following purposes: 

Providing,improving,and developing our products and services: We use personal data to help us provide,improve,and develop our products,services,and advertising.This includes using personal data for purposes such as data analysis,research,and audits.Such processing is based on our legitimate interest in offering you products and services and for business continuity.If you enter a contest,or other promotion,we may use the personal data you provide to administer those programs.Some of these activities have additional rules,which may contain further data about how we use personal data,so we encourage you to read those rules carefully before participating. 

 Communicating with you: Subject to your prior express consent,we may use personal data to send you marketing communications in relation toRCMENTproducts and services,communicate with you about your account or transactions,and inform you about our policies and terms.If you no longer wish to receive email communications for marketing purposes,pleaseContact Usto opt-out.We also may use your data to process and respond to your requests when you contact us.Subject to your prior express consent,we may share your personal data with third party partners who may send you marketing communications in relation to their products and services. 

Offering and measuring targeted advertisements and services: Subject to your prior express consent,we may use personal data to personalize your experience with our products and services and on third-party websites and applications and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. 

NOTE: For any of the uses of your data described above that require your prior express consent,note that you may withdraw your consent by support@rcmoment.com. 

 Promoting safety and security: We use personal data to help verify accounts and user activity,as well as to promote safety and security,such as by monitoring fraud and investigating suspicious or potentially illegal activity or violations of our terms or policies.Such processing is based on our legitimate interest in helping ensure the safety of our products and services. 

**2..Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies to provide,protect,and improve our products and services,such as by personalizing content,offering and measuring advertisements,understanding user behavior,and providing a safer experience. 

You can remove or reject cookies using your browser or device settings,but in some cases doing so may affect your ability to use our products and services. 

**3.Disclosure of Personal Data**

We make certain personal data available to strategic partners that work with us to provide our products and services or help us market to customers.Personal data will only be shared by us with these companies in order to provide or improve our products,services,and advertising;it will not be shared with third parties for their own marketing purposes without your prior express consent. 

_3.1Service Providers  _

We share personal data with companies that provide services on our behalf,such as website hosting,email services,marketing,sponsoring of sweepstakes,contests,and other promotions,auditing,fulfilling customer orders,data analytics,providing customer service,and conducting customer research and satisfaction surveys.These companies are obligated to protect your data and may be located wherever we operate. 

_3.2Corporate Affiliates and Corporate Business Transactions  _

In the event of a merger,reorganization,acquisition,joint venture,assignment,spin-off,transfer,or sale or disposition of all or any portion of our business,including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings,we may transfer any and all personal data to the relevant third party. 

_3.3.Legal Compliance and Security  _

It may be necessary—by law,legal process,litigation,and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence—for us to disclose personal data.We may also disclose personal data if we determine that for purposes of national security,law enforcement,or other issues of public importance,disclosure is necessary or appropriate. 

We may also disclose personal data if we determine in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our rights and pursue available remedies,enforce our terms and conditions,investigate fraud,or protect our operations or users.

_3.4.Legal Basis For The Processing of Personal Data from EEA Residents  _

It may be necessary—by law,legal process,litigation,and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence—for us to disclose personal data.We may also disclose personal data if we determine that for purposes of national security,law enforcement,or other issues of public importance,disclosure is necessary or appropriate. 

If you reside within the European Economic Area(EEA),our processing of your personal data will be legitimized as follows:Whenever we require your consent for the processing of your personal data such processing will be justified pursuant to Article 6(1)lit.(a)of the General Data Protection Regulation(EU)2016/679("GDPR").If the processing of your personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract between you and us or for taking any pre-contractual steps upon your request,such processing will be based on GDPR Article 6(1)lit.(b).Where the processing is necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation,we will process your data on basis of GDPR Article 6(1)lit.(c),and where the processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests,such processing will be made in accordance with GDPR Article 6(1)lit.(f). 

**4.Your Rights**

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is accurate,complete,and up to date.You have the right to access,correct,or delete the personal data that we collect.You are also entitled to restrict or object,at any time,to the further processing of your personal data.You have the right to receive your personal data in a structured and standard format.You may lodge a complaint with the competent data protection authority regarding the processing of your personal data. 

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data,we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such data,as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain.There are instances where applicable laws or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide or delete some or all of the personal data that we maintain. 

You may  Contact Us to exercise your rights.We will respond to your request in a reasonable time frame,and in any event in less than 30 days. 

**5.Third-Party Websites and Services**

Our websites,products,and services may contain links to or the ability for you to access third-party websites,products,and services.We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those third parties,nor are we responsible for the information or content their products and services contain.This Privacy Statement applies solely to data collected by us through our products and services.We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any third party before proceeding to use their websites,products,or services. 

**6.** **Data Security,Integrity,and Retention**

We use reasonable technical,administrative,and physical security measures designed to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to your data,and to correctly use the data we collect.For example,access to your personal data is restricted to our employees,contractors,and agents who need access to such data to perform their assigned job duties. 

It is important that you take precautions to protect against unauthorized access to yourRCMENT products,account credentials,and computer or other devices.If you feel that the security of your account or personal data has been compromised,please immediately Contact Us.Please be aware that,despite our best efforts,no security system is impenetrable.In the event of a security breach,we will promptly notify you and the proper authorities if required by law. 

We will retain your personal data for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement,unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**7.Data Transfers,Storage,and Processing Globally**

When we share your personal data with our partners,RCMENT-affiliated companies,and service providers,your personal data may be transferred to and/or made accessible from countries out of the European Economic Area.In such circumstances,we will enter into model contractual clauses as adopted by the European Commission,or rely on alternative legal bases such as the Privacy Shield,where applicable,or binding corporate rules where our partners or service providers have adopted such internal policies approved by European data protection authorities. 

**8.Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may periodically change this Privacy Statement to keep pace with new technologies,industry practices,and regulatory requirements,among other reasons.We expect most such changes to be minor.Any non-material changes will take effect immediately upon posting of an updated Privacy Statement. 

However,there may be cases where changes to the Privacy Statement may be more significant.In such cases,we will first provide a more prominent notice. 

Your continued use of the our products and services after the effective date of the Privacy Statement means that you accept the revised Privacy Statement.If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Statement,please refrain from using our products or services and contact support@rcmoment.com. 

Contact Us 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or its implementation,please contact us. 

Our email address is: support@rcmoment.com. 

  * Follow us

Newsletter

Enter Email Address get special discounts   
and exclusive promotions!
